{
    "id": "18ac08c90c3543b589fb6d1a979984ed",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This painting is older ……………………. that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How is this different …………………….. that?",
            "description": "Different can be followed by from, to or than.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "than",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that boy …………………… the blue shirt?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am waiting ……………………….. a call from my mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly it occurred ……………………. me that I hadn’t locked the door.",
            "description": "If something occurs to you, you suddenly remember it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She insisted …………………….. my joining her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He abstains ……………………… smoking and drinking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You must refrain ……………………… binge eating.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Some rogues had set the house ………………………. fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am thinking ……………………….. quitting my job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "over",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His friends egged ……………………… him to run faster and faster.",
            "description": "To egg on somebody is to encourage them.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nothing could stop him ……………………… pursuing his goal.",
            "description": "Stop is followed by object + from.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}